Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Research Files, 1770-2006; I
  - North Carolina, 1820-2005 (bulk 1880-2005); E
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Bluff Branch, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Bluff Branch School (1915-1925), 1916-1926 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: John Jackson Kirkland (Bushwhacker), 1928-1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Roxie McClure Overshot Mill, 1944, 1987-1997 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: M. A. Anthony Mill, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: James M. Hyde Grist Mill, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: John Kirkland Mill, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: George J. Johnson Grist Mill, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Tsali (Cherokee) Shot, 1914-2004 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Chambers Family, 1875-1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Chambers Creek, 1894-2000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Collinwood, 1972-2003 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Collins Family, 1883-1957, 1985-1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Trail of Tears, 1909-1993 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Richard Walker (lost land in 1828), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Major General Windfield Scott, 1919, 1994-1998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Scott's Creek (also Chambers Creek), undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: President Andrew Jackson, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Scott's Creek (now Chambers Creek), 1891-1914, 1987-1998 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Welch Family, 1873-1947, 1986-1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Chambers Creek Missionary Baptist Church (1886-1943), 1892-1997 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Chambers Creek School (1867-1925), 1893-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Forney's Creek, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: World War II Irritates Japan, N.C., undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Japan, N.C., Post Office, 1942-1996 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Camp Scott, N.C., undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Guardhouse Mountain, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Petroglyph Trail, 1987-1996 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Junaluska, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Cherokee Chronological Order (events span 1880 to 1995), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Fort Lindsay, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Bushnell, 1889-2003 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Captain Nimrod S. Jarrett's Killer Hung (1874 May 6), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Swinging Bridge at Bushnell, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Bushnell Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Bushnell Missionary Baptist Church, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Odd Fellows Lodge No. 238 (Bushnell), 1909-2000 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Carolina & Tennessee Southern Railway, 1895-2003; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 62, Folder 11] (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Smoky Mountain Railway Company, 1905-1994; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 62, Folder 12] (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Fish Trap Branch, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Monteith Family, 1872-1989 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Tuckaseegee River, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Topton, undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Fishtrap Branch, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Graham County Railway Company, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Ellis C. Monteith, J. P., undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: 1st Woman to Vote, 1895, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Ed Welch Hydroelectric Plant, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Pounding Mill, undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: A. J. Moore Mill, undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Jacob C. LeQuire Grist Mill, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Jasper Washington Anthony Grist Mill, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Little Tennessee River Area: Anthony Family, 1881-1947 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney Coat of Arms ( Our Light is from God), undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney, N.C., 1890-2000 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney and Noland Creeks, 1902-1990 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Jenney Branch, undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Dr. Alvin Lafayette Prince, undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Norwood Lumber Company, 1910-1993; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 62, Folder 13] (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Gee, N.C., 1885-1915, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Killed Cat that Sucked Eggs, undated (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Poplar Flats Camp, undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Tuckaseegee Foot Bridge, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Dr. William B. Cole, undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Forney's Creek Area: John B. Hoyle Mill, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Forney's Creek Area: A. J. Moore, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Hampton Cole Grist Mill, undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Mills, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Woody Family, 1875-1959, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Slab Camp, N.C., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Forney's Creek Area:Norwood Lumber Company Railroad (1906-1925), 1995-2004 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney School (1918-1940), 1917-1991 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney's Creek School (Woody School), 1888, 1965-2002 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney's Creek Missionary Baptist Church (1872-1943), 1943, 1987-1998 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney's Creek School, 1903-1999; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 62, Folder 14] (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Pleasant Grove Missionary Baptist Church (1884-1887), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Woody, N.C., 1989, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Forney's Creek Area: T. W. Woody Grist Mill, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Thomas Woody Turbine Mill, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Forney Ridge Peak (5051'), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Big Stone Mountain (Now Siler's Bald) (5620'), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Siler Family, 1882-1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Siler Meadows Mining and Lumber Company, 1904, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Reverend Henry Hogue, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Reverend Henry Hogue, 1987, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Forney's Creek Area: CCC Camp 413, Forney's Creek, 1960, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Siler's Bald (5607'), 1931-1998; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 62, Folder 15] (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Monteith Cabin (4960'), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Forney's Creek Area: George D. Monteith, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Jenkins Knob (5587'), undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Double Springs Gap (5507'), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Red Ridge Camp, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Junction Camp, N.C., undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Monteith Camp, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Chimzy Knob (5590'), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Buckhorn Branch, Camp 6 (Norwood Lumber Company) (3320'), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Forney's Creek Area: Steeltrap Creek, Camp 14 (4200'), undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 58, Folder 13] (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Clingman's Dome: Thomas L. Clingman, 1897-2000; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 1] (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Clingman's Dome: Clingman's Dome (6643'), 1890, 1937-2005 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Clingman's Dome: Camp 15 (Norwood Lumber Company), 1980-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 2] (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Clingman's Dome: Mount Buckley (6582'), 1874-2006; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 3] (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Clingman's Dome: Mount Love (6415'), 1914-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 4] (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Clingman's Dome: Hoyle Cemetery (TVA C49), 1942, 1986-1994 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Clingman's Dome: Woody Cemetery (TVA C10), 1909-1994; [Oversized Materials Removed to 63, Folder 5] (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Clingman's Dome: Branton Cemetery (TVA C47), 1936-1943, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Clingman's Dome: Lower Noland Cemetery (TVA C46), 1916-1944, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Clingman's Dome: Noland Creek No. 3 Cemetery, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Clingman's Dome: McClure Cemetery (TVA C12), 1942-1943, 1984-1994 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Clingman's Dome: Posey Cemetery, 1928-1942, 1986-1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Clingman's Dome: Welch-Anthony Cemetery (TVA C35), 1942-1943, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Clingman's Dome: Anthony Cemetery, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Clingman's Dome: Wiggins Cemetery (TVA C48), 1942-1943, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Clingman's Dome: Douthit Cemetery, 1928-1929, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Clingman's Dome: Tsali's Burial, 1975-1988 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Clingman's Dome: Woody Gap Indian Burial, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Clingman's Dome: Sassafras Knob Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Clingman's Dome: Hyde Cemetery, 1928, 1942-1943; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 6] (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Clingman's Dome: Monteith Cemetery (TVA C11), 1942-1943, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Clingman's Dome: Cook Cemetery (TVA C36), 1942-1943, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Clingman's Dome: Poplar Flats Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Clingman's Dome: Dorsey Cemetery (TVA C14), 1942-1943, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Noland Creek Area: James Andreas Thompson (1823-1893), 1886-1891, 1955-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 7] (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Noland Creek Area: Andrews Bald (5860'), 2002-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 8] (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Noland Creek Area: Harris and Woodbury Lumber Company Railroad, 1906-1991 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Noland Creek Area: Charles J. Harris, 1944, 1987-2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 9] (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland, N.C., 1900-1999 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Noland Creek Area: Harris Woodbury Logging Flume (1906-1918), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Noland Creek Area: Pole Tram Road (1903-1906), 1904, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Noland Creek Area: Mount Mitchell, 1913-1953, 1995-1996; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 63, Folder 10] (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland Flume Company, 1906-1910 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Noland Creek Area: Decker Lumber Company, 1916-1974 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Noland Creek Area: Pole Town, undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Noland Creek Area: Wolverine Lumber Company (Pole Road), 1903-1988 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Noland Creek Area: W. T. Mason Lumber Company, 1879-1922 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Noland Creek Area: Philip G. Rust, 1944, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland School (also Bear Pen School), 1911-1941, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Noland Creek Area: Telephone at Noland, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland Swinging Bridge, 1923, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Noland Creek Area: Arnold E. Bradshaw, undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Noland Creek Area: Mason Lumber Company, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Noland Creek Area: Bald Creek Sawmill Town (1906), undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Noland Creek Area: Lower Ripshin Sawmill Town (1908), undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Noland Creek Area: Salola Branch Sawmill Town (1910), undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Noland Creek Area: Eversole Lumber Company Explosion (1897), undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Noland Creek Area: I. K. Stearns House, 1953, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Noland Creek Area: Solola Valley, N.C., 1988-1989, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Noland Creek Area: Mill Creek, 1921, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Noland Creek Area: Mill Creek School (1915-1929), 1916-1928 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Noland Creek Area: Branton Family, 1915-1993 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Noland Creek Area: Pole Road School (1905-1909), 1905-1937 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland Creek CCC Side Camp 413, undated (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Noland Creek Area: Hickory Flat Branch, 1880-1989 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Noland Creek Area: Roy Cook Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Noland Creek Area: Narrows Indian Cemetery, undated (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Noland Creek Area: Kitchen Door Cemetery, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Noland Creek Area: Bradshaw Place Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Noland Creek Area: A. E. Bradshaw Family, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Noland Creek Area: Cabin Door Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Noland Creek Area: Conner Cemetery (TVA C34), 1915-1920, 1942-1943, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Noland Creek Area: Stiles Cemetery (TVA C38), 1909, 1919, 1942-1943, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Noland Creek Area: Watkins Cemetery, 1888-1928, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Noland Creek Area: Millsap Cemetery, 1854-1903, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Noland Creek Area: Conner Cove Cemetery, 1928-1989 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Noland Creek Area: Rust Electric plant, 1922-1954 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Noland Creek Area: E. B. Jenkins Mill, undated (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Noland Creek Area: E. O. Hall Mill, 1915, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Noland Creek Area: Goldmine Branch, 1975-1989 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Noland Creek Area: Reverend Evion O. Hall Overshot Mill (Goldmine Branch), 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Noland Creek Area: Tunnel Ridge (Indian Gold Mine) (2840'), 1967, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Noland Creek Area: Reverend Evan D. Hall (Minister & Teacher), 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Noland Creek Area: Jim Ute Ridge (4400'), 1887, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Noland Creek Area: Jerry Bald (5140'), undated (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Noland Creek Area: Reverend Evion O. Hall Cemetery, 1914, 1943, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Noland Creek Area: Reverend Andrew Jackson Hall Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Noland Creek Area: Lewis Hall Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Noland Creek Area: Elias Hyatt Cemetery, 1880, 1914, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Noland Creek Area: Cole Hyatt Cemetery, 1916, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Noland Creek Area: John Fuller Cemetery, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Noland Creek Area: Tunnel Gap Indian Burial, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Noland Creek Area: Goldmine Gap Indian Burial, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - Noland Creek Area: Noland Divide, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Noland Creek Area: Road to Nowhere, 1990-2004 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Mount Collins: Collins Gap (5723'), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Mount Collins: Mount Collins (6188'), 1937, 2000-2005 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Mount Collins: Meigs Post, 1829, 1929-2005 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Mount Collins: Black, Ellen Englemann. Diffusion of an Isolated Mountain Community, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Mount Collins: Swain County, N.C., Board of Commissioners (1871-1929), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Mount Collins: North Carolina, 1975-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Mount Collins: N.C. Park Commission, 1939 December 31 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mount Collins: Charleston, N.C., 1965-1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Jackson County: Jackson County, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Charleston Township: Deep Creek Township No. 1, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Charleston Township: Elder Humphrey Posey, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Hickory Flat Branch: Hickory Flat Branch, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs, 1876-1994; [Oversized Materials Removed to 63, Folder 11 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Epps Springs: Epaphroditius Everett, 1873-1970, 1987-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Epps Springs: Caldwell House Hotel and Mineral Springs, 1884-1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Epps Springs: John R. Snow Overshot Mill (Peachtree Creek), undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Epps Springs: Abraham L. Nichols Overshot Mill, 1895-1928, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Epps Springs: Hyatt Mill, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Epps Springs: Silas Ball Mill, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Epps Springs: J. E. Bird Grocery, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Epps Springs: Shadrach Hyatt, 1885, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Epps Springs: Dr. Robert L. Davis (practicing in Epps Springs in 1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Epps Springs: Ozzie Ball (Confederate Soldier), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Epps Springs: Ball Family, 1871-1947, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Epps Springs: Ball Falls, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Epps Springs: DeHart Family, 1940, 1987-1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs Missionary Baptist Church, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs School (1908-1943), 1909-1943, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Epps Springs: DeHart School (founded by a former slave), 1887, 1965, 1984-2000 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Epps Springs: Talc Mine, 1949 November 24 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Epps Springs: Feldspar Mine Deaths (1943 March 15), 1934 March 18 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Epps Springs: Kaolin, 1889 August 22 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Epps Springs: Kaolin (fine china clay), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Epps Springs: Harris Clay Company, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Epps Springs: Kituwha (Governor's Island), 1975-1989 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Epps Springs: Cooper House (home of Horace Kepart), 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Epps Springs: Prisoners Chained to Road Work, 1895, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Epps Springs: Arlington Baptist Church Cemetery, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Epps Springs: John S. Smiley, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Epps Springs: Jackson Tine Cemetery, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Epps Springs: Raymond H. Muse, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Epps Springs: Ruffin DeHart Cemetery, 1872-1945, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Epps Springs: Will J. Woodard Cemetery, 1886-1945, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Epps Springs: Peach Orchard Indian Cemetery, 1904, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Epps Springs: Burns Cemetery, 1878-1956, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Epps Springs: James H. Holden Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Epps Springs: Peach Mountain Indian Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Epps Springs: Mine Mountain Indian Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Epps Springs: Charlie C. McLean Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Epps Springs: Lands Creek School, undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Epps Springs: Dan Schuler (Bear Hunter), 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Epps Springs: Great Smoky Mountains Railroad, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Epps Springs: Road to Nowhere, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Epps Springs: Noland Divide (6200'), undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Epps Springs: Bryson City Interviews, 1895-1942, 1988-1997 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs Cemetery, 1989 July 19 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Epps Springs: Eagle's Nest Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs Cemetery/Shadrach Hyatt, 1986, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Epps Springs: S. M. Hyatt Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Epps Springs: Tumbling Waters Indian Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Epps Springs: Rock Bar Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Epps Springs: High Falls/Millsap Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Epps Springs: Turner Bill/Sherrill Wiggins Cemetery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Epps Springs: High Falls/John A. Millsap Cemetery, 1878, 1891, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Epps Springs: Garden Spot/Charles Bazzle Cemetery, 1881, 1908, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Epps Springs: Peachtree Cemetery, 1929, 1943, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Epps Springs: Massie Gap (3000'), 1895-1998 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Bryson City: Fred Cline Shot by Bushwhacker (1866), 2003 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Bryson City: Lucy Ann Cline, undated (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Bryson City: Bryson City, 1914-2000 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Bryson City: Town of Bryson City, 1889-1908, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Bryson City: Alarka Valley Railroad (1915-1929), 1987-2004 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Bryson City: Yonaguska Reservation (1736'), 1820, 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Bryson City: Andrew Jackson Lambert Hanged (1887 July 4), 1987-2005 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Bryson City: Rural Free Delivery Established, undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Bryson City: Sawmill Explosion Kills 5 (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Bryson City: Spittoons Necessary to Open Courthouse (1908), undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Bryson City: Newspapers Published since 1889 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Bryson City: Lightning Rod Salesmen Taxed (1928), undated (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Bryson City: Funeral Cost $38.40 (1923), undated (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Bryson City: Bryson City Telephone Company (established 1906 February 5), undated (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Bryson City: Typhoid Vaccinations (1923), undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Bryson City: Practicing Physicians (1923), undated (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Bryson City: Stock Law Brings Fences (1895), undated (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Bryson City: Dr. Joel A. Cooper (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Bryson City: Dr. James H. Teague (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Bryson City: Dr. James P. DeHart (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Bryson City: Dr. Aurelius McDonald Bennett (1861-1941), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Bryson City: Dr. E. M. Scruggs (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Bryson City: Dr. Gaston M. Massie (1893), undated (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Bryson City: Moonshining was Big Business (1923), undated (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Bryson City: Reverend P. P. McLean (1889), 1889-1896 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Bryson City: Spread of Sawmills after 1878, undated (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Bryson City: Tuckaseegie Ferry (1891), undated (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Bryson City: Yonaguska, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Bryson City: William B. Garrett, undated (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Bryson City: Great Smoky Mountains Railway (General), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 94)